<Document>
  # Suspicion on Space Station Rules

  Glossary:
  - RDM\n
    RDM stands for Random Death Match. This is when a player kills another player without a valid reason.
  - Metagaming\n
    Metagaming is when a player uses information that their character would not know to their advantage. This includes using information from OOC chat, deadchat, or other sources that their character would not have access to.
  - OOC\n
    OOC stands for "Out of Character".
  - IC:\n
    IC stands for "In Character".

  Use votekicks if an admin isn't online to deal with a rulebreaker.

  Any gameplay rules such as RDM, metagaming/metacomming, etc. are not enforced after the round ends.

  1. No bigotry, racism, or hate speech.\n
     This includes slurs, hate speech, and other forms of discrimination.\n
  2. No metagaming.\n
  3. No RDM.\n
     RDM involves killing another player without a valid reason. Once is fine, but repeated offenses will result in action being taken.\n
     This rule does not apply to traitors.\n
     Stuff like "Do not come into my house or I'll shoot you" is not a valid reason.\n
     Alive-checks so, "Are you alive? I'll kill anyone who doesn't respond" are also not valid reasons.\n
  4. Do not delay the round as a traitor without a valid reason.\n
  5. Do not post IC information in OOC chats, unless the round is over.\n
  6. Do not post OOC information in IC chats.\n
  7. Do not use exploits to your advantage, if you are unsure if something is an exploit, ask an admin.\n
  8. This is an NRP server, however names that reference real-life figures are not permitted.\n
     Meme names are also fine as long as they are not something inappropriate.\n
     For example: You can name yourself "The Traitor", but something like "Mr. Beast" is not allowed.\n
  9. Please be kind to other players.\n
     No harassment, bullying, or other forms of toxicity.\n
  10. No ERP.\n
     Any form of ERP will result in a ban; I mean, come on, it's a game about killing each other. Not a dating simulator.\n
  11. English only.
     This is an English-speaking server, so please speak English in OOC and IC chats.\nWe cannot moderate other languages.\n
  12. Do not perform major sabotage as an innocent.\n
     This includes blowing up generators, setting of nuclear options near a lot of people or where it will do a lot of damage due to spacing in a hallway.\n

</Document>
